<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coffees on Shikonn's brain cell</title><link>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/</link><description>Recent content in Coffees on Shikonn's brain cell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Shikun</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 17:03:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kentucky Bourbon Barrel Aged From Cooper's Cask Coffee</title><link>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/coopers_barrel_aged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 17:03:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/coopers_barrel_aged/</guid><description>Barrel Aged Coffee Boxed Set
Coffee info: Roaster Cooper&amp;rsquo;s Cask Coffee Note Chocolate hazelnut, seet plums, roasted nuts with a bourbon finish Roast medium dark Region Colombia I love cold-brewing barrel-aged coffe beans. Whenever I am brewing at home or drinking the brewed coffee at office, the ambient space instantly is filled with dense whiskey/bourbon aroma. My coworker was asking &amp;ldquo;Who is consuming alcohol?&amp;rdquo;, lol.</description></item><item><title>Don Pepe Farm-level Reserve from Verve Coffee Roasters</title><link>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/verve_don_pepe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 16:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/verve_don_pepe/</guid><description>DON PEPE GESHA HONEY FARMLEVEL RESERVE
Coffee info: Roaster Verve coffee Roaster Producer Pepe fallas Origin Single Origin Process honey Note golden raisin, honeysuckle, lime Roast light roast Region costa rica Variety gesha This is my first farmlevel reserve coffe, and it is as good as expected! It is so full of aroma, and there is no too explicit fruity/herbal/chocolaty note. The notes are subtle and well-balanced. I feel like it is better served hot and its aroma makes you feel relaxed.</description></item><item><title>The Future Tequila Sunrise from BLACKWHITEROASTERS</title><link>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/thefuture_blackwhte/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 23:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/thefuture_blackwhte/</guid><description>The Future - Tequila Sunrise | Cofermentation | Black &amp;amp; White Coffee – Black &amp;amp; White Coffee
Coffee info: Roaster Black and White Coffee Roaster Producer SNAP Specialty Coffees, Jairo Arcila, and Wilder Lasso Origin Blend of 5 Process 2 anaerobically fermented ethiopia, 3 co-fermented (one with passionfruit, one with lychee, one with lemon) from columnbia Note fresh citrus, red raspberry, pink bubblegum, tropical Roast light medium Region Ethiopia and Colombia Variety various It is very fruity, maybe the most fruity one among all the coffee I&amp;rsquo;ve had in my life.</description></item><item><title>LAYO 5 from LOVELESS COFFEES</title><link>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/loveless_layo5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 13:02:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/loveless_layo5/</guid><description>Coffee info: Roaster LOVELESS COFFEES Producer Layo Teraga Co-op/Hawata Washing Station Process washed, 72 H fermentation Note jasmine, honeysuckle, stonefruit Roast medium to light Elevation 1950-2300 MASL Region Uraga, Guji Variety semi-forest Ethiopia Heirloom Resting Period 2+ weeks Brewing method: Water temp 205 F Grind ODE SSP 4+1 Ratio 23:350 Bloom 46 Pour 104, 100, 100 Coffees from this region - particularly around Hawata Washing Station - are some of the highest grown coffees in Ethiopia with some farms topping out at 2300m.</description></item><item><title>Hamasho from ILSE COFFEE</title><link>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/ilse_hamasho/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:36:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shikunsh.github.io/coffee/ilse_hamasho/</guid><description>Coffee info: Roaster ILSE Coffee Process washed Note lemon, limeade, jasmine, melon Roast medium to light Elevation 2300+ MASL Region Bombe, Ethiopia Brewing method: Water temp 205 F Grind ODE SSP 4+2 Ratio 23.5:350 Bloom 47 Pour 103, 100, 100 It tastes fruity with a hint of flowers. It&amp;rsquo;s very light and there is not too much acidity or bitness.The clean, fresh aroma is typical of washed coffee.</description></item></channel></rss>